People of God, Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Yuriy and I am from Ukraine.
The SCOAN is really a church of all nations. Let's praise the Lord for this.
Yuriy - Emmanuel TV Testimony
I want to tell you how Emmanuel TV really changed my life.
About two years ago, my wife and I started watching Emmanuel TV
and it greatly affected our marital life, relationships and my spiritual life.
When I watch Emmanuel TV, I receive a message,
some kind of revelation for myself each day.
Tell us, brother: How did you actually discover Emmanuel TV, all the way in Ukraine?
I was browsing on YouTube and found some interesting videos
about deliverances and prophecies by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I really got interested because I had never seen such deliverances and miracles before.
I got interested in what Prophet T.B. Joshua was doing.
About six months ago, an incident happened in our family.
You see my wife here.
One day, she was at home with our baby boy.
She just bent down to pick him up and something snapped in her back.
When I came into the house, I saw her lying on the floor and the baby was crying.
I tried to pick her up but it took me almost ten minutes to pick her up.
The pain was so intense that I had to lay her down on her side
and she laid there for nearly two days.
I had to roll her to move her because she couldn't move on her own.
We called the doctor and the doctor came and did some kind of massage
but nothing good happened; she rather got worse.
At that point, she was basically completely crippled. She couldn't walk, she couldn't move.
Absolutely. She couldn't move or walk.
In the evening of the second day, I decided to go to YouTube
to find videos of healing prayer for viewers with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Here, you can see in the picture how we were just touching the screen.
As you know, distance is not a barrier.
God filled my heart with belief that I could touch the screen
and then, touch my wife and God would touch her and heal her.
We prayed for about one minute and at one point,
I felt something moving inside of us.
I saw that my wife just stood up and started to bend down and to the left and right.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sir, as you prayed with Prophet T.B. Joshua on YouTube,
a prayer he had prayed for viewers around the world,
the power of God descended in your house in Ukraine, and your wife received her healing.
Yes, she received her healing and started moving and checking herself.
I even asked her what she was doing because she couldn't move before.
She went and dressed up on her own, without my help
and we went to testify to our parents for what God had done in our lives.
Wow! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Ever since then, sir, how is your wife since that prayer
she offered with Prophet T.B. Joshua? What is her condition since then?
She feels absolutely wonderful. She is in Ukraine with our two sons.
God is blessing us very much. Praise the Lord.
Hallelujah. We can see the pictures here.
Can you just show us again. Who is this lady?
Her name is Julia.
Wow, we can see her testifying here after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV,
how she received her healing instantly in the name of Jesus Christ.
Brother, what can you tell the world about Emmanuel TV
and especially how you encourage people to pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua
on Emmanuel TV, anywhere they are in the world.
I'd like to say to the whole world that Emmanuel TV is really a gift of today.
You may not be able to come every day to The SCOAN
because you may live very far from here but distance is not a barrier.
You can watch Emmanuel TV and God will raise your spiritual life up.
If there is any trouble or affliction in your life or any problem of any kind,
you can pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua and God will move in your life.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Once again, this is a great encouragement for those who are living a very far distance
from the church here in Lagos, Nigeria. You may physically not be able to come
but by faith, join with Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV
and the same power of God working here will touch you anywhere you are all over the world.
Even if you can't access Emmanuel TV on satellite,
on the internet Emmanuel TV is streaming 24/7
and there are also many wonderful clips on our official YouTube channel
which you can connect by faith with and God will touch you as well.
Brother, we thank God for your life, and we know the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Thank you.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.